{
    "questions" : [
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_1_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Can you take a look at this? I spilled coffee on my clothes.\nMan : Shall we take a look? Well......, it will be clean if you wash it. Until when should I do it for you?\nWoman : Please do it by tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_2_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "35_3_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  먹든지",
            "option_2"      : "②  먹거나",
            "option_3"      : "③  먹고 나서",
            "option_4"      : "④  먹다 보면",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Can you take a look at this? I spilled coffee on my clothes.\nMan : Shall we take a look? Well......, it will be clean if you wash it. Until when should I do it for you?\nWoman : Please do it by tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  먹고 나서",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "4. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  기다리게 해서 죄송합니다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  내일은 꼭 나가도록 하겠습니다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  감기에 잘 걸리지 않는 편입니다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  오늘 못 가게 되면 전화 드리겠습니다.",
            "detail"        : "Man : Boss, I don't think I can go out today because I have a cold. I'm sorry.\nWoman : It's okay. By the way, did you go to the hospital? There are many other people, so don't worry and take a good rest.\nMan : I will make sure to go out tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  내일은 꼭 나가도록 하겠습니다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "5. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  제시간에 도착해서 다행이에요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  기차가 예정보다 늦게 오겠는데요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  일을 하느라 기차를 놓칠 뻔했어요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  비가 와서 그 시간까지는 힘들겠는데요.",
            "detail"        : "Man : Welcome, sir. Where do you want me to take you.\nWoman: Seoul Station. By the way, sir, can I get there by 7 o'clock? I have to take the train.\nMan : It must be hard until that time because it's raining.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  비가 와서 그 시간까지는 힘들겠는데요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "6. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  안 그래도 다 팔렸더라고요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  어제 벌써 하나 사 왔어요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  저도 한번 만들어 보려고요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  저도 가게에 가서 사야겠어요.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : The drinks you make at home are popular these days. The way to make it is simple and easy, so they make a lot.\nMan: I make it myself, so it's better for your health than selling it.\nWoman: I'm going to make it, too.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  저도 한번 만들어 보려고요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "7. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  거실이 좀 넓으면 좋겠어.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이따가 몇 개 더 갖다 놓을게.",
            "option_3"      : "③  그럼 저쪽으로 옮겨야겠네.",
            "option_4"      : "④  화분이 없어서 허전한 것 같아.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : The living room was so spacious that it looked empty, but it's much better to put a few flower pots like this?\nMan: Yes, but I think it would be a little uncomfortable if there was a big flower pot next to the door.\nWoman: Then I'll have to move over there.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  그럼 저쪽으로 옮겨야겠네.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "8. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  신청서만 쓰면 빌릴 수 있어서 참 편해요.",
            "option_2"      : "②  빌려가는 사람들이 생각보다 적었나 봐요.",
            "option_3"      : "③  우산은 내일 출근하는 길에 갖다 드릴게요.",
            "option_4"      : "④  필요할 때 빌릴 수 있어서 좋았는데 아쉽네요.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Well, it suddenly rained, so can you still borrow an umbrella these days?\nMan : What should I do? The umbrella rental service has been suspended since last month. There are too few people returning umbrellas, so it's hard to continue the service.\nWoman: It was good to be able to borrow it when I needed it, but it's a pity.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  필요할 때 빌릴 수 있어서 좋았는데 아쉽네요.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "9. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  침대의 사진을 찍는다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  침대를 만든 회사에 연락한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  가게로 침대를 가져간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  중고 가게에 가서 침대를 산다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : I heard you buy furniture from a secondhand store. I'm thinking about selling a bed, what should I do?\nMan : First, take a picture of the bed and post it on the store's website and write down which company it is from. Then the store will contact you.Then do I have to bring the bed?\nMan : No, people from the store will come and take it.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  침대의 사진을 찍는다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "10. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  복사기를 수리할 사람을 찾는다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  복사기의 종류와 가격을 조사한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  구매팀에 복사기 상태를 설명한다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  사무실에서 쓸 복사기를 사러 간다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Team leader, I think we need to buy a new copy machine.\nMan : Why? You can't fix it?\nFemale : Yes, the copier is so old that it's going to cost a lot to fix. Why don't you talk to the purchasing team and buy a new one?\nMan : I do. Then you can tell me the details.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  구매팀에 복사기 상태를 설명한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "11. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  인문학 강의를 신청한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  남자와 함께 강의를 듣는다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  교재를 사러 서점으로 간다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  홈페이지에서 교재를 확인한다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Minsu, are you going to take a humanities class this time?\nMan : I heard it last year. The Lecture is so popular that you will have to apply quickly.\nWoman : Oh, yes. Then we'll have to hurry. By the way, what is the textbook? It wasn't on the homepage.\nMan : Really? I have the book, so I'll bring it to you tomorrow.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  인문학 강의를 신청한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "12. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  현장학습 일정을 짠다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  체험관의 위치를 알아본다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  자연재해를 체험해 본다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  체험관의 프로그램을 확인한다.",
            "detail"        : "Man : Mr. Kang, where should we go for this field trip?\nWoman : Well, how about the Safety Education Experience Center? Experiencing natural disasters such as earthquakes will be beneficial to students.\nMan : That would be great. I'll have to find out specifically what kind of programs are there are. I'll check the location, too.\nWoman : I'll find the location for you.\nMan : Really? Thank you, Mr. Kang. Then I should make a detailed schedule.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  체험관의 위치를 알아본다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "13. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰은 물건 값이 싸서 세일을 안 한다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰 물건은 한국보다 가격이 더 비싸다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰에서 물건을 주문하는 방법은 복잡하다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  해외 온라인 쇼핑을 하면 물건을 받을 때까지 오래 기다려야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman: I heard it's cheap if you buy something at an overseas online shopping mall?\nMan : Yes. It takes a little long, but it's much cheaper. You can buy things that you can't get in Korea.\nWoman : Isn't it complicated to order? I'm thinking of trying it too. Man: It wasn't very difficult. It's cheaper if it's on sale, so take a good look at the sale period.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  해외 온라인 쇼핑몰은 물건 값이 싸서 세일을 안 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "14. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  공원에서 영화를 상영할 것이다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  영화 촬영 때문에 공원에서 나가야 한다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  영화 촬영하는 모습을 사진으로 찍을 수 있다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  동문 주차장에 있는 차를 다른 곳으로 옮겨야 한다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : I will give you guidance. After a while, the filming will be held from 4 to 7 pm. If you have parked your car in the east gate parking lot, please move it to another parking lot in the park. Photography is prohibited during filming, so please cooperate.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  동문 주차장에 있는 차를 다른 곳으로 옮겨야 한다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "15. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 공연은 어른들을 위해 기획되었다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 공연에는 어린이들이 무용수로 나온다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  공연 중에 내용 이해를 돕는 노래가 나온다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  이 발레 공연은 이번에 처음 하는 공연이다.",
            "detail"        : "Man : The following is the news of the encore ballet performance that became popular at the end of last year. This performance is a ballet prepared for children by a dance troupe made up of teachers from an art high school. Dancers dress up in animal costumes and dance for children to enjoy. Songs are also added to help children understand. It would be nice to see the whole family together for a holiday outing .",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  공연 중에 내용 이해를 돕는 노래가 나온다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "16. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  열차의 분위기는 현대적이다.",
            "option_2"      : "②  10년 전부터 카페를 운영하였다.",
            "option_3"      : "③  기차역과 열차를 카페로 바꿨다.",
            "option_4"      : "④  카페 손님은 주민들이 대부분이다.",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Today, we are at Songjeong Station, a train station where there are no trains. Stationmaster, please introduce this place.\nMan : This is a place where trains have not been running for 10 years. So I haven't been using history. A recent suggestion from a resident made a train station and train into an old train-like cafe. The response of the local residents is good, and more tourists come after hearing the word of mouth of the guests who visited this place.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  기차역과 열차를 카페로 바꿨다.",
            "score"         : "2"
        }
    ]
   
}
